yusrablog.com 2012-05-20

# Privacy Policy | YusraBlog.com

YusraBlog is committed to respecting the privacy concerns of its visitors to the blog. YusraBlog has created this privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to establish guidelines that will govern the collection, use, and disclosure of the personal and non-Personal Information of its visitors.

YusraBlog collects three kinds of information from the Websites:

  1. Your voluntarily provided Personal Information
  2. Anonymous Non-Personal Information
  3. “Cookie” Based Information.

 **Personal Information:**

YusraBlog does not automatically collect Personal Information, such as name, residential address, phone number, email address and other personally identifiable information, from its visitors (“Personal Information”).

From time to time, YusraBlog will collect Personal Information that is voluntarily provided by its visitors in filling out email forms and subscribing to newsletters via feedburner and other activities carried out on the Websites.

YusraBlog will only collect, use and disclose Personal Information after the visitor has voluntarily agreed to such collection, use and disclosure. YusraBlog also sometimes use email addresses that have been voluntarily provided by its visitors to respond to visitors who communicate with us, to allow subscription to newsletters and other services.

All emails from YusraBlog to its visitors include instructions on how to discontinue receipt of emails, newsletters and other communication from YusraBlog and visitors can discontinue such communication at any time. Email addresses from visitors who wish to discontinue receipt of YusraBlog emails will be removed from YusraBlog distribution lists.

All Personal Information that may identify a visitor and has been collected with the visitor’s consent by YusraBlog is not disclosed in any identifiable form to any other party outside the company except for the fulfillment of the specific purpose identified to the visitor at the time of collection, or as may be required by law.

YusraBlog may disclose such information in anonymous, aggregated and non-personally identifiable form to other parties for marketing, advertising or other purposes and to better understand visitor’s use of the Website. At any time, a visitor may send an email via [**contact page**](http://www.yusrablog.com/contact/ "Contact Us") to request that Personal Information be reviewed, changed, removed or updated in YusraBlog databases.

Visitors should exercise caution when they disclosed personally Personal Information in comments on the websites. Such areas are accessible by anyone and may result in the visitor receiving unsolicited messages from other people and/or companies. Although YusraBlog is committed to protecting the Personal Information provided to it by its visitors in compliance with this Privacy Policy, it cannot guarantee the security of information, whether personal or otherwise, that visitors disclose online to publicly accessible bulletin boards or chat rooms.

 **Anonymous Non-Personal Information:**

When visitors visit the Websites, anonymous, non Personal Information about their visit is automatically collected. Such information may include the length and date of the visit, how the visitor navigated the Websites, what pages the visitor viewed, the type of browser being used by the visitor, the type of operating system used by the visitor and the domain name of the visitor’s Internet service provider. YusraBlog uses this Anonymous Non-Personal Information to track the success of its Websites with its visitors and to better tailor the Websites to visitors’ needs and interests. This Anonymous Non-Personal Information may be shared with other parties, such as broadcasters, advertisers, sponsors and partners.

 **Cookie-Based Information:**

YusraBlog may use cookies on its blog. “Cookies” are pieces of information that a website transfers to a visitor’s hard drive for record keeping and identification purposes. Cookies are used to make the visitor’s use of a website easier by saving visitor preferences and passwords and to identify which areas of the website are popular and which areas need improvement and how to target certain advertising to its visitors. YusraBlog does not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information except in connection with a password protected online registration for a contest or newsletter or other service and only with the visitor’s informed consent. Visitors may visit the Websites with its cookies turned off to avoid the collection of Cookie-based Information.

 **Protection of Visitors’ Personal Information:**

YusraBlog protects the Personal Information it collects with appropriate technological (firewall, password protected servers), physical and administrative safeguards to protect if from unauthorized disclosure or use. Access to Personal Information collected by YusraBlog is limited to authorized individuals. YusraBlog retains the Personal Information only for as long as is required for the purposes identified at the time of its collection and consented to by the visitor providing it or as otherwise required by law. Once Personal Information is no longer necessary for the purposes consented to by the visitor, YusraBlog will delete it from its data bases or make it anonymous.

 **Linked Websites:**

The Websites may have links to other websites. These linked websites are not under the control of YusraBlog. Visitors should ensure that they read and understand how their Personal Information may be collected, used, and disclosed by the linked websites as YusraBlog is not responsible for and shall not be held liable for any procedures, policies or activities of any websites linked to the Websites.

 **Advertisers:**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on YusraBlog. Our advertising partners are,

  1. [ **Google Adsense**](http://www.google.com/adsense)
  2. [ **CpxInteractive**](http://www.cpxinteractive.com/)
  3. [ **Infolinks**](http://www.infolinks.com/)
  4. [ **MGID**](http://www.mgid.com/)

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

 **Visitor’s Consent to Privacy Policy:**

By visiting and using the YusraBlog, the visitor agrees to the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service included with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy or Terms of Service, do not use the Websites or provide Personal Information.
